Chung, PeiYun (Lu)

<u>lu.pychung@gmail.com</u> +886 910 075 741

OBJECTIVE

My enthusiasm is to design new systems, which intensify people's ability and boost their quality of life. With practical experience in visual communication and interaction, enthusiasm, creativity and skills drive me to further explore the area of data visualization, advancing the field of human-computer interaction and the ability of research plan.

EDUCATION

National Kaohsiung Normal University, Taiwan

Master of Fine Arts in Visual Design

Thesis GPA: 4.0/4.0

Sept. 2013 - Jun.2016

- Academic Excellence Award secured one gold medal and one silver medal for overall excellence.
- Thesis: Semiology on The Little Prince The study of semiology in the animation, The Little Prince (2010). Analysis of visual style, cultural meaning and integrated research of the previous publications.

Bachelor of Design in Visual Design

GPA: 3.91/4.0

Sept. 2009 - Jun. 2013

- Academic Excellence Award secured three gold medals and two silver medals for overall excellence.
- · Final Year Project: Devised Space Design, Animation Video and Publications in Ingenuity Exhibition
- Awards: Ingenuity (Vision Get Wild Award, 2013), Pop-up Desire (HTC Packaging Awards, Silver Prize, 2011)

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer - SHOPLINE Inc., Taipei

Feb. 2017 - Present

- Designed *Merchant App* interfaces and conducted prototype interaction testing, creating the customer service to 8,000+ merchants as one of the key contributors to the company and product.
- Prototyped new POS (Point of Sale) system and devised the user flow of the transaction process, product inventory and order management as the combo service product of ecommerce shop and in-store business.
- Revamped *Admin* platform and storefront website with hi-fi prototypes on computers, tablets and mobiles, which is the major project to product teams increasing the profitability 120% in five months.
- Integrated *Design Guideline* consistent with the current corporate identity system, which is consisted of the parts created by the other three designers involved as the principle of product interface improvement.
- Customized *PLUS* website and prototyped new screens and interaction across multiple devices, which provides customer satisfaction to all 5 participants increasing the revenue over \$30,000 USD in ten months.

UI Desinger - Al Group Corp., Taipei

Oct. 2016 - Dec. 2016

- Engineered front-end web design for the art museum big opening campaign with the architect institutions.
- Designed *JUT App* for the building and employee management of JUT Land Development Group., an architectural enterprise with approximately 100 people.

UI Designer - Techgiant Inc., Taipei

Feb. 2016 - Aug. 2016

- Innovated the project Robelf visual identity and logo design, which primarily sustained the crowdfunding campaigns.
- Devised touchscreen interfaces and voice user interfaces with elegant hi-fi prototypes both on the tablet and mobile for *Robelf* mechanic products, which raised roughly \$150,000 USD funds in one year on Indiegogo.
- Organized and planned Robelf web design, identifying solutions, prototyping validations, and designed the related graphics such as production-timeline illustration and commercial photography.

SELECT SKILLS

Computer Graphics: VI Design, Data Visualization, Multimedia Design, Photography, 2D and 3D Computation Design: User Interface/experience design, Interactive Prototypes, Web Design (HTML/CSS/JavaScript)

Software: Sketch, Framer, Illustrator, Indesign, Lightroom, Photoshop, Premiere, After Effects, Autodesk Maya Traditional Media: Pen/marker Drawing, Pastel Art, Watercolor, Acrylic Painting, Oil Painting